Whenever your heart is broken
Don't ever forget,you're golden
I will find a light in your soul I'll be there（I'll be there）
-
Never leaving you in the darkness
Even when you're out of focus
I will be the light in your life You'll see clear
-
I'll be your INSPIRATION
Cause I know that you do just what you're told
I'll be your heart and temptation
Cause I know that you'll make it on your own
-
Baby you can count on me now
When you're falling down, down, down
I will find a light in your soul, I'll be there（I'll be there）
-
Leaving your love is the hottest
Even when you're out of focus
I will be the light in your life, you'll seek rare
-
I'll be your INSPIRATION
Cause I know that you do just wipe your toe
I'll be your heart and temptation
Cause I know that you'll make it on your own
-
I'll be your INSPIRATION
Cause I know that you do just wipe your toe
I'll be your heart and temptation
Cause I know that you'll make it on your own
-
waaaa~~
yeah~yeah~
wuuu~
yeahhhh~